outbetting
Kanamin bought four of them a souvenir
pudding, but...
One of them...
One of them was eaten?
Yes, one of them was eaten by someone.
What's this?
And the message on the pudding was...
It's your turn, Hiyori.
Who ate the pudding?
Wasn't it Kanamin?
It wasn't me. I bought four.
But it says it's Hiyori's turn.
So it's Hiyori's turn next, right?
Then who ate it first?
I wonder who it is.
But Hiyori's...
I don't know.
What does that mean?
It means there's someone who ate it
before Hiyori, right?
But there's a possibility that Hiyori
ate it first and wrote it to hide it.
Because he didn't write it.
But the same...
Piyo? What's Piyo?
You know, Juri said, this is a voice-
shaping app, and the cake and ice cream
are goodbye for a while.
You said that, right?
But the cake and ice cream mean that
the pudding is...
That's right.
I don't know.
The cake is...
I'm on a diet, so I don't eat pudding.
I eat ice cream, though.
Then let's split it up.
No!
I see.
What do you mean?
You said you don't eat it, right?
Yeah, but I didn't eat it.
But if we split it up, this game is
over.
I won't be late.
But you like to eat.
I like to eat, but I ate cutlet rice
bowl this morning, so I don't have any
pudding left.
You're lying.
You said you'd split it up.
But I ate rice balls earlier.
You ate it while you were buying it.
You love pudding, don't you?
So I bought it because I wanted to eat
it with everyone.
It's lonely to eat alone.
I bought four because I wanted to eat
with everyone.
But you had a dream when you were a
kid, right?
You ate a bucket of pudding, right?
I ate it.
Did you eat it?
That's why you like it so much.
I like it.
My childhood dream was to eat all the
pudding in the world.
That's a good dream.
You want to eat all the pudding in the
world.
That's right.
Isn't that Kanamin?
Kanamin's face is red.
I said something weird.
I'm embarrassed to say it myself.
You're a liar.
That's right.
I can't see Jiria's face.
I can't see it.
But this is different.
Jiria...
Boyopi?
No.
I'll go again.
Before Jiria went to the bathroom, I
was a little flustered.
I thought you were eating alone.
I didn't eat.
You didn't eat?
We came together when we came here
today.
I bought pudding.
You bought it, right?
But when Hiyori opened her eyes,
Kanamin ate it.
It took me a long time to eat it.
I see.
Did you eat it and come in?
Or did you put it in the refrigerator?
We didn't know you would buy it.
Jiria is always late.
Haru is always early.
But I was late today.
It's raining, so I'm a little late.
It's raining on the way.
It rained just before I walked here.
I often experience that.
It rains as soon as I get out of the
house.
I'm sick when I get to the venue.
I see.
It's unfortunate.
I opened the refrigerator and found
something delicious.
There is a refrigerator at the
entrance.
Is that so?
I didn't know that.
That's what you might think.
But Hiyori might have changed the way
Kanamin eats.
That's why you're wearing sunglasses.
You're going to see 4DX together.
So, you might be hiding it.
You two might be different.
Did I eat it while I was here?
You didn't.
To be continued.
They might be covering each other.
No, no.
I want to eat.
I want to eat with everyone.
I want to eat a lot too.
But there's one more thing.
I guess so.
It's Hiyori's turn.
It's just a paper.
Yeah.
What?
A cell phone?
I'll press play.
I see.
Here is a hint from AI Hito-chan.
Hitoka?
Eh? Hito-chan?
AI?
AI Hito-chan.
What does that mean?
It's a hint. But it's a hint.
A hint?
Next, Semi.
Did you look under the box?
Under the box?
What? There's something written on it!
Wait, wait, I can't get it out.
There's something written on it. I'm
scared.
What? I'm scared.
9, 49, 46, 32, 21, 6
What?
4, 4, 4
I'm sorry.
I didn't get a 2.
616, 622, 638, 629.
What's 46?
Was there 46?
No.
The person who ate it?
There was 46.
The result number is 6.
21.
Even though it's 21.
I don't know. I don't know at all.
How many are there?
Tell me.
46 minus 32.
14.
I don't think I can tell.
32 minus 21.
11.
Then why 6?
Isn't it scary?
Thank you for watching.
I'm sorry.
Don't make it sound like it's okay.
Isn't it scary when it's a scene like
this?
47 minus 21.
40, right?
I think I've drawn a few.
46 minus 21.
Draw all of them.
25?
24.
14.
46 minus...
46 minus 46 is 0.
Then...
Then, it's 40, 25, and 14.
I can't count them all.
14, 15, 16, 17, 18...
What?
I got it!
I'm sorry, I can't do that.
What do you think 46 means?
You got it?
I got it.
You're smart.
46 is...
It's the number from A to U.
And the 6th one, 46...
What's the 6th one?
The 21st one is...
The 32nd one is me.
The 46th one is me.
It's you!
It's Kanarin!
I got it!
It's you!
I'm scared.
I can't believe it's Kanarin.
She'sbehaving like now.
Thank you for the meal!
Thanks for watching!
I'll check with AI Hito.
It's Unru!
It's a prank!
What is this?
You're too into it.
I've seen all the episodes.
You're good at this.
I'm excited.
I was so nervous.
I'm nervous.
You're lame.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to eat this.
We did it!
The first time to perform live in front
of the audience
I want to perform live in front of the
audience
I will show you a more powerful
performance than last year
Thank you for your support
We are really thankful
Our history story has just begun
I think that if we all do it, there's
no way we can't do it and there's an
infinite number of possibilities.
If we're with Senzenbei and the
members, we can definitely make a big
wall into a small wall.
So, wait for us, Nakano Sampler!
Dash! Dash! Dash!
Never waking up from this dream
Because I can be with you
I can be happy
I'm not happy
It was delicious! Thank you!
Thank you!
Can I have a tissue?
It's like...
It's so far away!